Bon appétit.
It's delicious.
It's so good!
Oh, my God, I'm hooked.
I wish I was.
It's a different color.
Yum! Yum!
Hello, everyone.
Hello.
I'm Shizuki Yamashita from Fukuda High 46.
I'm with Mukai.
Yay!
This is a ramen project. Yesterday, the Aichi leg of the tour was over, and the next day, we went to Ise.
This time I asked Ito to join us.
Yes, I do. I love spicy food, don't you?
I also like spicy food, as you all know, so this time we both want to eat at Ise-san.
Yay!
What are your favorite dishes at Ise-san and Ise-san?
What's your favorite dish?
Is this the most mainstream?
Haima Ramen?
I guess this one.
This is probably the most popular one.
Two pepper marks
Oh, my God!
I can't imagine...
Two pepper marks...
A big surprise?
I was afraid of the "big surprise" while I was dealing with the big one.
I spent more than 60 yen for one...
Oh, my God, that's scary.
What should I do?
Oh, my God.
Does it look spicy?
I think it's scary.
Do you want to try all three?
Spicy. Pain
What?
I'll go up one and make it 3.
I don't know.
Do you want to go up 3?
Why don't you try 3?
I'll try three.
What?
I'm not sure I'm good enough for C.
Well, I'll try three.
I'll try 2.
I'm scared.
Okay.
One more bowl of Taiwanese ramen and one more bowl of Taiwanese ramen.
One more of Taiwanese Ramen with one more spicy spicy spicy spice.
3 hot peppers with 3 hot peppers
Three hot peppers.
Yes
and a coke and orange juice.
Coke and orange juice.
Do you think it's spicy? But...
I already had spicy ramen yesterday.
Doesn't that sound good?
Does it look good?
What's he like? I'm curious.
It's just Taiwanese noodles.
Thank you.
It's warm.
It looks spicy.
Compact size
I was thinking...
I had ramen in Osaka, and it was pretty spicy.
Looks spicy
Looks spicy!
Looks really delicious! Looks so delicious!
Yes, ma'am.
This is it.
Oh, I think I got it.
Let's drink.
I like youtubers.
I don't know, it's different from what I've already seen.
No, it's not.
That's so cool!
You can do it. You can do it.
Okay, okay.
I'm satisfied.
Well then, Seenosan, yes, let's eat.
Oh no, it's delicious.
Looks really spicy.
There is a lot of meat in it.
Every bowl of soup comes with chili peppers.
Oh, no!
It's delicious. It's easy to eat.
The spiciness is easy to eat for me.
It's spicy.
Spicy, but delicious. It's crazy.
I think it is quite spicy from the bread.
The meat is also spicy.
It's really tasty.
It's quite sticky,
It's almost like Chinese noodles,
I'm sure.
Maybe it's that kind of noodle.
In my opinion, it is better not to slurp too vigorously.
They are similar.
Yes, for sure.
Yes, it is.
If you rinse it, it's called "swallowing.
It goes like this.
Delicious. Delicious.
It's so delicious.
This is just my opinion, but it goes really well with cola.
It's amazing.
Yes, it is.
It goes really well with coke.
I would also like to say that orange juice goes well with it.
Oh, it's delicious.
Orange goes well with orange juice.
It's delicious.
It's good.
Good?
Yummy?
Good night.
Tastes a little sweet.
Is it the noodles that are sweet?
Noodles are noodles, and noodles are noodles.
It's delicious.
Try the regular one.
What do you think?
Maybe our tongues are bugged.
What was that?
I'm trying to make it hotter, and you're trying to make it the same.
It feels the same when we take turns.
I know.
That's why I said maybe it's the same.
I'm scared.
Oh, man.
Bon appétit.
It's not too spicy?
What?
Really spicy?
Sweet!
Jacking?
Sweet.Sweet.
It's sweet. It's totally different.
I can't see.
Just eat it.
My tongue is already twitching.
It's sweet.
What?
Sweet.
Wow.
But...
It's hot
Thank you very much
Very nice!
It's true that increasing the spiciness by one level may make a big difference!
It's just my opinion.
If you like spicy food with acid, you can enjoy it.
Dainpai? Normal "Dai-hai" might be a little bit sweet.
If you think it's good at first, you may want to go for acid.
I really don't know what I'm talking about.
But it's still spicy.
The color is definitely red, and the amount of chili is different.
But you know what I mean?
It's the taste.
It doesn't matter which one you eat, it's the same.
I'm used to it.
I don't know.
It's starting to taste sweet again.
It's so good, I'm hooked!
Oh, man!
I can't believe it's Mirika!
It tastes like axe!
Mire-kaa-kaa-kaa!
n trаst
T misunderstanding
I always go with Mio, but she's really not good at it.
If she had come today, she would have cried already.
That's for sure. It's true.
I couldn't tell if it was hot or spicy.
But it's been on my tongue for a long time now.
The end.
One more time.
Can I have another Coke?
One more Coke.
I know it's hard to do without a drink.
Coke... when you've had your drink.
I'll have another drink.
I'll have a Coke.
I've never eaten ramen so slowly
I've never eaten ramen so slowly.
I've never eaten ramen so slowly before.
It doesn't take me 20 minutes to make ramen today.
It only takes about 10 minutes, right?
I'm weak right now.
I like spicy food, but I'm weak.
It was delicious.
I haven't eaten there in a while.
Is it good?
Delicious.
It's good, but it's really spicy.
It's spicy.
It's good.
Are my lips thicker than in the beginning of the video?
It's true.
I love the way she looks at me when I say it's spicy.
It's delicious.
"It's delicious!
I hope you like it.
You ate well.
It's delicious.
Yum! Yum!
Okay. heave-ho!
Thank you for the food.
That was delicious.
It was delicious.
It's like spicy food in the hot summer.
I think I crave it after a workout or something like that.
If you eat it in winter too...
It's so good.
It keeps you warm.
That's true.
It's warm right now.
It's so hot.
But here...
It's a little tingly, but it's really good.
It was delicious.
I'm Miyo Matono of Sakurazaka 86, and this is Shizuki Yamashita.
Yesterday, the Kanagawa show was over, and we've just finished the last leg of the tour.
We're going to Tokyo Dome in June, and today is the last show of the tour.
Today is the day!
I'm here at the original Mutantanmen Honsha!
This restaurant is very famous in Kanagawa.
Is it a little spicy?
It's our first time here.
We came here for the first time today after the Kanagawa concert.
I'd like to eat something spicy to cheer up my stamina after the Kanagawa show today.
I'm starving!
Yay!
It smells like fried rice over here!
New cup
Indeed.
Now, let's choose by running!
I'm going to order a phantom.
I think I'd like to order Phantom.
I heard you can choose how spicy you want it.
I'm not a big fan of spicy food, so I'm going to order a Phantom.
I'm not good at spicy food.
I'm not good at spicy food, so I'd like to try a little less spicy. I'd like to try a little understatement.
Moderate is what?
Yellow peppers.
Not even one, but a forced yellow pepper.
They say it's safe for children.
This one's a little too red.
Let's go with medium hot.
I'll make it medium hot.
You can see the picture.
It's very spicy.
If you've had it, please let me know.
I'd like you to use it as an example.
What kind of noodles?
If I put one medium spicy and one low spicy
And one medium hot.
Yes, it's done!
Thank you very much.
I'll be waiting for you with the third one, medium spicy.
Okay, bye-bye.
Not too spicy.
Are you sure?
Yes, please eat.
Okay, have you eaten?
I'm good.
Did you eat it?
Yes, I ate.
It's good.
Yay.
Looks good.
Bon appétit!
Ladies, this one's not dirty.
Hmm?
Not one step dirty.
I recommend the sauce drink.
Oh, you mean with a straw.
Not a straw.
It's delicious.
We went to the movies the other night, right? We went to the movies the other night, right?
We went!
We went to the movies together.
We went to the movies.
We've been going to a movie together since last year.
We saw the previews and said we wanted to go.
It finally came out.
We saw it.
It was scary.
Scary.
Is this okay?
I have something to say.
The day me and mio...
Me and mio went out for a glass of wine that day.
Oh, my God.
I want to thank you.
Thank you very much.
I always come to you when I'm about to say something.
From outer space.
Thank you very much.
Wow, wow, wow.
It's a different color.
From outer space?
From outer space.
Just a little bit.
Out of space.
I'm coming out of space.
Now.
Okay.
Okay, I'll take it.
Yes!
You got it!
Oh, wait.
Wait.
Thank you for watching. Thank you for watching!
When you are hungry, open your stomach.
If you are hungry, we will open your stomach.
Thank you.
Spicy marshmallows.
Oh, that's nice.
Not at all as this fantasy.
Bon appétit.
Spicy.
I'm looking forward to it.
Looks delicious. But it looks spicy.
It looks really spicy.
I wonder if the restaurant in Rio is not spicy at all anymore.
I heard they have spicy food at Kitayama, right?
I wonder if it's spicy.
Oh, Ranri is huge.
Wow.
Is it great?
It's a bad idea to slurp it up again.
Oh, wait.
Oh, my God.
Sorry.
This soup is really good.
It's definitely not spicy.
I'm sure it is.
Good job.
Good work.
Delicious.
It's so huge.
Sticky.
Delicious.
It's so delicious.
I think mine has a pretty light soup, and the noodles are sticky. It's so smooth.
Very sticky.
This is medium hot.
It's quite warm.
It's totally fine. It's totally fine.
Really?
I think it's pretty okay.
Hmmm...
It's really good.
Is it spicy?
Mmm.
It's good.
What the hell?
Why didn't it go to 7?
Tiran 3, right?
I want to put it in 3.
I think it's good.
I think it's a good idea.
I think it'll work.
It's hard.
Painful
painful
spicy
Mmm
Certainly the noodles are not spicy
Oh, it's spicy
Spicy
It wasn't spicy.
Not at all.
It's good, right?
I can see the soup is spicy.
I don't care how hot it is.
I don't mind the spiciness.
You can eat it without worrying about the spiciness.
I'm not sure if it's moderate or normal.
Normal people.
Uh-huh.
Mnh-mnh.
Mm-hmm. Mmm.
The eggs...
They're good.
Kakitama is delicious, isn't it?
It's so good!
I love it so much!
Wow.
Mmm.
Mnh-mnh.
It's so good. It's so good.
So good. So good. So good.
Mmm.
Mnh-mnh.
I've tried many kinds of ramen
There are so many different kinds of ramen.
Yes...
I've seen so many different kinds of delicious ramen through this project.
Delicious!
Yeah, I'm happy.
Yeah.
There's a place called "Meat & Gleep
There's a place called "Meet & Greet" where we can talk.
Since I've been in Tokyo.
Do you have any recommendations for ramen shops? Like that.
Yes.
I'm often asked.
I really want to know.
On the contrary, I'd like to know.
You don't have to go. I have to go.
I want to explore the stores in Tokyo, too.
Yeah, I know.
I was so hungry.
I'll keep going. I'll keep going.
Mmm.
Mnh-mnh.
Noodles are gone.
Mmm
Mmm.
Mnh-mnh.
Thank you for watching!
It is very tasty.
Looks estaba feliz.
I'll be right back home, tomatoes ripening.
Who can eat canaimo?
I can eat canaimo.
I'll eat them!
romssäo
Ahmal deer tongue
kola
Delicious!
I'm out of noodles too.
It's so good!
I think these eggs are absolutely delicious!
Yum! Yum!
Good. - Good. All right. - All right.
Thanks for the food.
It was really delicious!
The noodles were different from any other ramen I've ever had.
It's one noodle and it's sticky.
It was so smooth and easy to suck!
I chose medium spicy this time.
Next time, I'm definitely going to try the very spicy one.
The hottest!
If you like spicy food, I'd like to show it to you!
Is it written that it is extremely spicy?
Surprise!
I want to be surprised!
I will definitely go again!
I want to try it!
Spicy
Spicy!
Very tasty and delicious!
Thank you for the food
Thank you very much